( Watch on Kissasia.vip & KonFlix.vip )
=Lady Liberty=
=Episode 22=
(Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui)
(Chapter 51: Such is Fate)
(Dingqi Reading Platform)
(Qin Han, the Yan bounty assassin,
awakens from his crushing defeat.)
(Chapter 51: Such is Fate)
(Dingqi Reading Platform Real-time Data)
Let's celebrate.
To our new author, Sansan.
If Lin Zhanqiao
knew you were Sansan,
what then?
I don't know.
But she'll find out eventually.
So,
does Zhao Lanxin
treat you better
than Lin Zhanqiao
in the partnership?
That's why I wish
Lin Zhanqiao would
treat me like Zhao Lanxin does.
So you still prefer Lin Zhanqiao.
Er Jiu asked me today.
He asked if I'd consider
marrying him.
Makes sense, I guess.
If you aren't
going to marry me,
I might as well marry Er Jiu.
It's not like I'm
a successful woman like Lin Zhanqiao.
I must
find someone while I'm
still young.
They want someone
they truly like.
They won't marry
unless they're madly in love.
We just need someone we don't hate.
I like you.
But I don't hate Er Jiu.
Er Jiu says
his feelings for me are genuine.
Haven't you already
made your choice?
(Esports Cafe Arcade)
(Chapter 51: Such is Fate.
Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui, Sansan)
(To have his life dictated by others...)
Mei.
Did you just get back from Jiangxi?
Got back this afternoon.
I dropped by my place first.
Did you see Lawyer Bei?
Problem solved?
He's making up the difference.
And I don't have to deal with the rest.
That's pretty stand-up of him.
Weren't you worried
he'd skip out on the debt
and leave to hide from you?
He didn't lie to me
or use me.
He took responsibility.
He just did
what he was supposed to do.
If he had thrown you under the bus
to take the blame,
that would just mean
he's a terrible person
with character flaws.
Well, what he's doing now
doesn't make him noble,
nor is it love.
Let's not lower the bar here.
Mrs. Bei found out.
She demanded that
I sever all ties with Lawyer Bei.
She's that calm
and forgiving?
I've only met her once,
but I get the feeling
she's not that simple.
Unless she was prepared.
Sparkling water.
Here.
Thank you.
Mrs. Bei.
Sorry, I'm late.
Well?
Did you bring what I asked for?
No.
You just refuse to give it to me.
I believe this matter
ends here.
Ends here?
It's six million yuan.
Just like that?
After what I've sacrificed,
it just ends here?
This actually
has nothing to do with Zhou Mei.
Mr. Bei needed someone
to be his corporate proxy.
If not Zhou Mei,
it would've been someone else.
But right now,
it is Zhou Mei, not someone else.
Lawyer Bei's biggest mistake was
choosing such a beautiful woman
to act as his proxy.
Right?
Yes.
My girlfriend is beautiful.
But because she is my girlfriend,
I can't let baseless accusations
be pinned on her.
I am a lawyer.
I know how easily things can escalate.
Are you serious?
Is Zhou Mei your girlfriend,
or...
Or is she Lawyer Bei's girlfriend?
Mrs. Bei, I'm serious.
She is my girlfriend.
Fine.
I just wanted to teach her a lesson.
I wouldn't actually send her to prison.
In my eyes,
Zhou Mei didn't break any rules.
If you think she played by the rules,
I'll be the judge of
whether she crossed the line.
It was Mr. Bei who crossed the line.
True.
His biggest violation
was getting involved with Zhou Mei.
Fine.
You take your Zhou Mei.
And I'll manage my husband.
Working with you
has been quite pleasant so far.
It ends
if things go south.
Who's bothering you this late?
Your phone's blowing up.
It's my dad.
He sent a bunch of apartment listings
all at once.
Have you listed the place?
Any inquiries?
The housing market is terrible.
I had to drop the price a bit.
The agent said it was
the only way to sell it.
Plus,
I'm in a rush to sell.
The requirements I gave my dad were
cheap rent,
convenient transportation,
and three bedrooms.
Why so proactive?
I was afraid you guys would ditch me.
So I took the initiative.
Once we start making some money,
I'll buy a bigger place.
Great.
I'll ask my dad.
Let me forward these to our group chat.
If you see anything you like,
my dad can arrange a viewing anytime.
Ms. Lin.
You finally found
a favor my dad can help with.
You can't escape us now.
What...
What is it?
My dad sent something about you.
Me?
Things about Zhou Mei?
What is this about?
My dad
knows a lot of rich wives, right?
You know how it is.
Whenever a good property pops up,
he sends it to them.
They can buy it on a whim.
Get to the point.
So...
In that wives' group chat,
someone posted a photo of Mei
with her business profile.
Why? What for?
What do you think?
"Beware of this homewrecker."
I'll just read it out loud.
(She has the face of a seductress.)
"Watch closely.
(Don't let her exploit vulnerabilities.)
Are your husbands
(I don't want any more victims.)
associating with this woman?
If so, you must...
You must
beware of this gold digger.
She has cost Mr. Bei six million yuan.
If a hotshot like Mr. Bei
lost money to her,
imagine what she's capable of."
That's it.
Who posted this?
It must have started with Mrs. Bei.
No one else knows about this matter
except Mrs. Bei, Mr. Bei
Zhang Yousen and me.
Will this affect you, Mei?
No.
It's just a bit annoying.
I'll have to deal with gossip.
Is she okay?
When it comes to
handling people like them,
she never loses.
They're carving up your client list.
The gossipers went
to the Boss this morning.
Led by the worst of them,
they rattled off your list
of married male clients.
They said you'd jeopardize the clients,
that they want to help
and retain these major clients.
Got it.
My clients used to be mine.
From now on,
I'll make sure their clients
become mine, too.
They know your clients
better than you do.
You know?
What intel did you provide?
I just provided emotional support.
I trashed you left and right.
I am the grandmaster
of adding fuel to the fire.
Didn't they give you any of my clients?
Please.
The mid-to-senior executives
are all Iron Ladies now.
I'm too busy serving them.
Are you done?
Hurry up and leave.
Stop blocking the way
like you always do.
A peacock would've
taken up less space.
Excuse me.
What is that supposed to mean?
You spit when you talk.
It's gross.
I really want to curse her out.
Alright, calm down.
Her days are numbered.
How did it go with the Boss?
Does the Boss know the rich wives
publicly shamed her?
She knows.
She was already planning
to discuss her role today.
What goes around comes around.
You mean Zhou Mei?
Who else?
Six million yuan.
It takes
skills to make a man
cough up six million.
He didn't pay it for me.
His own business had issues.
I don't need a man
to spend six million on me.
You've been
popular lately.
Since last night,
ninety percent of the calls
on my phone have been about you.
If these rumors
are causing issues
for my clients at home,
you can reassign their accounts
if they agree to it.
But Boss,
I doubt I'll lose
any of my clients.
I wouldn't have
lasted this long otherwise.
In sales,
it's not just women.
It's mostly men.
Anyone trying
to poach my clients is mistaken.
I make more money not by competing
against women,
but against men.
I haven't said anything.
Yet, you lectured me.
What?
You act like you don't care,
but you clearly do.
I do care.
I've known some clients
for seven or eight years.
I've nurtured
these relationships.
Did I tell you what the calls
were about?
What about?
A large part was just gossip, of course.
But others
were calling to work with you.
Partner with me?
It's a PR firm.
What they need
is connections, resources,
EQ, and crisis management skills.
In your scandal with Mr. Bei,
you demonstrated all three perfectly.
So, Boss,
are you saying
you want new clients
to replace my old ones?
Who was just telling me
that she is irreplaceable
to her old clients?
So turn off your internal alarm.
If I'm so important to the company,
does that mean
I can make a request?
What about the game rights for "Tao Yao:
Dream of Wuchuan"?
The same offer.
It's a reasonable deal for us.
Their boss is a fan of He Han.
Even after what happened,
they're willing to stick to the price.
This money is our lifeline.
He Han rejected the offer because it was
too low.
Get the contract moving.
Legally, the copyright belongs to us.
But morally speaking,
I should inform He Han.
Okay.
What's with Gu Yan?
I tested the waters with him.
He doesn't seem interested
in starting a new novel.
He said that's what you wanted.
He wanted to write a sequel
to "Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui".
You didn't approve it.
He swore up and down
that he had
the energy to start a project.
What about Sansan?
Aside from Mr. Fan and Zhao Lanxin,
nobody else knows Sansan's identity.
The credited editor is Zhao Lanxin.
The contact for
Dingqi Reading Platform is Mr. Fan.
No one else has handled it.
Is it possible
she's doing what you did with Gu Yan?
Hiding her own secret weapon?
Unlikely.
It's either
a sensitive background
or they're a famous author
using a new pen name.
Hong Qigong?
Different writing styles.
Is it possible
she changed her style?
Changing one's writing style
is very difficult.
Three bowls of wontons.
Your steamed buns.
- Thanks.
- That's everything.
I already paid.
- Great.
- Condiments are over there.
Who is it?
You're here about the new project?
Yeah.
You said you had the time
to start another one.
At the time,
I really wanted to write a sequel.
That's why I said that.
Later, I realized
I overpromised.
But you've been submitting
your drafts on time.
You told me
if I want to do this long-term,
I need a routine.
I've been telling you that since we met.
But you never took it seriously.
Why so disciplined
all of a sudden?
Submitting drafts on time
gives me time
to play games and relax.
A good work-life balance
makes the pressure
feel manageable.
You haven't reached out much lately.
Isn't that what you wanted?
Submitting drafts on time,
maintaining quality,
and not taking up
too much of your time and space.
That's the expected behavior
of a mature, independent author.
I did want you to grow up.
I have.
That way, you have the time
to develop other authors
and help them grow, right?
In theory, as an editor
or a boss,
that's what I should be planning.
But our situation now is different.
So I'm hoping
you can stand by my side
and help Chenxing
get through this difficult time.
I'm glad to hear you say you need me.
Because I always thought
that I was the only one
who needed you.
Yes, I need you.
I need you to start a new project.
So the company can
rely on you for more income
to keep operations running.
Why didn't you let me
write the sequel back then?
We wouldn't have these problems now.
That was Mr. Fan's advertising project.
A sequel to Phantom Knight
wouldn't have added
much to your personal value.
You're going to like
the story I have.
I told you.
I don't have the energy
to juggle two projects.
Chenxing and I
need your help.
Finish what you're working on.
Look at it when you have time
before you decide.
I'll wait to hear from you.
(The old man pointed
at the chessboard and said,)
("Every move represents destiny.)
(Your fates are like the pieces,
manipulated by others...")
I'm so sick of this.
HR is absolutely useless.
Shouldn't Zhou Mei get transferred?
Why is it you?
What did the Boss tell you?
The Boss just said
they're preparing to restructure
our current accounts.
Shouldn't Zhou Mei be kicked out?
Did you tell the Boss
your husband and in-laws
are all in Beijing,
so they're sending you there?
I didn't.
I said the rest of us
have some bandwidth,
and we want
to contribute more to the company.
You should have
just said you have bandwidth!
Why drag us into it?
I'm so sick of this.
What about
your local clients in Shanghai?
Well, we definitely have the bandwidth
to take those over.
Excuse me.
Sorry to interrupt.
The Boss told me to take over
your Shanghai clients.
Whenever you have time,
let me buy you a coffee.
Those three women out there,
can we fire at least one of them?
Their combined sales numbers
exactly equal mine alone.
If one leaves,
I'll take her clients,
and you save on a salary.
Show some mercy when you can.
That's what I wanted to say.
You really know
how to make women hate you.
I'm a woman.
I know exactly why they hate you.
I value you
because I am a boss.
I know what kind of employee
is more important.
So,
keep proving your worth.
Yes, Boss.
I won't let you down.
Why do we have to hand them over to you?
The three of us are the closest.
Our clients are interconnected.
We see each other all the time.
I'm going to the Boss.
That wouldn't be wise.
Stop bragging about how close
the three of you are.
Otherwise, the Boss might just
send you all to Beijing.
They are short-staffed there.
I'm not scared.
The one being transferred
should have been you in the first place.
Because you said I was a liability.
The Boss is keeping me in Shanghai.
Doesn't that solve your problem?
What problem?
What happened?
Nothing, yet you claimed
I was a problem.
Watch it, or I'll sue you.
Are you close with them?
Care to go to Beijing?
Now I'm really mad.
You messed with the wrong person.
(Shrimp and Fresh Meat)
That scared me to death.
I felt like
I was acting in "Infernal Affairs".
It's so exhausting.
My gosh.
I need some orange juice
to regain my strength.
How was my acting?
Manly, right?
Good enough for an Oscar?
Brilliant.
But I think White Tea
probably wants
to take you to Beijing.
Between Black Tea, Green Tea, and you,
she has to pick someone.
If she's thinking that,
you have to save me!
Your hand.
What for?
Your protection.
If White Tea drags you away,
tell the Boss
that Black Tea has a major client
moving to Beijing
for their kid's school.
She didn't tell the Boss,
so the Beijing team can't take them.
Then, I won't wait
for her to drag me down.
I'm going straight
to the Boss after this.
They never could have guessed
that trying to rat you out
would backfire
so spectacularly.
How did you find out?
They always pick on me.
I have to be prepared.
Brilliant.
(Mrs. Bei)
Hasn't He Han always
been at the top of the list?
The only reason he isn't this time
is because of the recent backlash.
Didn't I tell you?
I'll handle the backlash.
Without the resources,
how can I make money?
The fans of our top two books
have flocked
to the "Parting with Yan Dan
at Yishui" fan group.
Was that your doing?
Those are VIPs.
You think I could sway them?
They like He Han,
but that doesn't stop them
from liking other authors.
They can tip He Han,
and still
go over to
"Parting with Yan Dan at Yishui"
and tip there, too.
It's their choice.
Nobody should
put all their eggs in one basket.
Who are you talking about?
Who?
I mean nobody.
Me, you,
and even He Han.
Us.
He Han.
Can you please sit down?
What is he doing?
Riding a bike?
Did you say
the same thing to Zhao Lanxin?
"Us"?
That "us"
is different from this "us."
With her, it's strictly business.
Between us,
it's about loyalty.
Fan.
Only what translates
into cold, hard cash
is true loyalty.
Just be patient, okay?
Remember the former editor
for Phantom Knight, Ma?
I've been talking to him lately.
This guy, Ma...
He Han.
The Phantom Knight team
might release a statement soon.
They're willing to endorse
your "Shattered Six States".
Fan, are you for real?
I certainly hope it's real.
That's why I've been working
tirelessly on it.
How do you prove
the statement is actually
from Phantom Knight?
That's exactly the tricky part.
It depends on whether Phantom Knight
is willing to reveal his identity.
If he does,
it'll be a massive event
in the literary world.
Of course.
If this gets handled
this way,
doesn't that resolve He Han's crisis?
Right?
So,
just wait.
I'm afraid we can't.
Why not?
I plan to
end "Shattered Six States" early.
Why?
It's annoying.
Ending it early saves a lot of trouble.
When you say early,
how early do you mean?
Within three days.
You're...
You're just speaking out of spite.
Aren't you going to publish
what you've written?
No.
I'll talk to He Han.
You head back.
No, He Han.
It's impossible to end it in three days.
Didn't you just introduce a new map?
Who do you think makes up the new map?
Three days or three months,
doesn't it depend on how I write it?
Even being generous,
we've only written
not even half
of what's in the outline.
That's a terrible ending!
Listen to me.
We have a contract!
You'll be held liable.
It has a beginning and an end.
It's a proper ending.
How is it not terrible?
The story...
Go back. Let me talk to him.
Forget the ending and the contract!
- Don't we have an outline?
- Just stop talking, okay?
Just go.
Stop talking.
How will you face your readers?
I don't care, He Han.
Alright.
You go first.
Talk some sense into him!
I will.
He's gone.
Now tell me the truth.
What are you really planning?
I told you.
I'm ending
"Shattered Six States" in three days.
Your readers will tear you apart.
They already are.
Those are just
Phantom Knight's old fans
and some random
bystanders.
What about your own fans?
They're still on your side.
And as Fan mentioned,
if Phantom Knight
releases a statement,
this will all blow over.
My novel is my novel.
My story, my voice.
Why should someone else have to vouch
for my own work?
What if there's no statement?
Am I the problem?
Or my novel is?
That's nonsense.
I don't care about a statement.
Once I finish "Shattered Six States",
it's over.
I'll just write a new story
that's better than this one.
You'll pay damages!
Then I'll pay!
I work for you to make money.
How much more do you want?
I'll give you every cent I have left.
Will that do?
Fine.
I'll do it.
Now I know
why Lin Zhanqiao couldn't stand you.
When things are easy,
you're nice and smiling.
But when they aren't,
you flip the table and quit.
You're an adult.
You can't expect life
to be smooth sailing every day!
And you can't expect those around you
to always have your back,
tolerating every erratic mood
and every outburst,
while they pamper you
and worship your attitude!
Go figure it out!
Hello?
When are you free tonight?
I have meetings all afternoon.
Not sure when I'll be off.
Let me know when you're done.
Okay.
The company's operational issues
are a heavy burden for us.
But I'll handle that.
That pressure must not
bleed into the project.
Haste makes waste.
We need to maintain
our current development pace.
A unique edge
goes a long way.
Quality over speed.
Zhangzhu.
Why are you distracted at work?
Mr. He Han posted in the group
that "Shattered Six States"
ends in three chapters.
What? Why?
He said he wants to write a new novel.
Meeting's over?
Are you here
to tell me you're ending
in three chapters and 10,000 words?
It's the only way to stop you and Ma
from trying to unmask Phantom Knight.
Ma and Fan have only
talked a few times.
Fan is a shark.
You think he'd pass up a gimmick
like exposing Phantom Knight?
He'd love for me
to keep writing and taking the heat
just to set up the big reveal.
Everyone wants a piece of that drama.
I have to end this now
to catch him off guard.
You're sabotaging your future.
You have ways
to solve this problem.
Why choose a path where everyone loses?
I'm not here to argue.
I've made my decision.
I'm just letting you know.
You didn't have to notify me.
Also...
From now on,
stay out of my business.
I was your editor
when "Shattered Six States" began.
I want it to have a proper ending.
I did, too.
But it seems impossible now.
Are you lying to yourself?
Maybe you should thank Fan.
He gave you the perfect excuse
to mask your incompetence.
Don't be silly.
The story's father-son relationship
was your main driver.
You don't believe in it anymore,
so you can't write it.
Since the day your father died,
you've been stuck.
In the story, the son
is hunted by his father for miles.
He kills his father to survive.
But in reality,
after your father passed away,
you regretted it.
Regret for not forgiving him.
Regret for holding onto your anger.
You got the story wrong,
but now it's too late.
Yes.
I just can't write it anymore.
It's not just because of him.
It's you,
Lin Zhanqiao.
Because
"Shattered Six States" is our story.
That's why I want to end it.
I think it's time...
But regardless,
I want you to keep writing.
Don't give up.
Give it a proper ending.
Lin Zhanqiao,
aren't you overstepping a bit?
It's just a novel to pay for drinks.
Why take it so seriously?
If one story ends badly, write another.
Since you love studying relationships,
why don't you look at your own parents?
Their relationship is so twisted,
and it would make for a great novel.
Maybe the company would
actually get funded.
Then, you could finally be successful
instead of being stuck
in this wreck,
waiting for it to go bust!
What is wrong with you?
Do you think I like bossing you around?
It serves you right that you're stuck.
You deserve to be called a plagiarist
and have the world turn on you.
Whether you sink or swim,
I'm finished with you.
Whatever novel you write,
I won't give it a second look.
Please don't.
It's an eyesore.
♪I keep asking myself♪
♪What it is I should become♪
♪To follow what my heart truly wants♪
♪Like a drifting dandelion♪
♪Turning where it drifts♪
♪Into soil where it can grow♪
♪When the rain comes, I hide♪
♪In a flower shop at the corner♪
♪Even spring borrows its fragrance♪
A can of beer.
♪Across fields of blooms,
a boat awaits me♪
♪Swaying in the shape of the wind♪
Do you still like her?
♪I want to go on like this♪
Yes.
Very much so.
♪This moment is worth
more than anything♪
(In that moment,)
(both He Han and I)
(had reached our breaking point.)
(Driven by desperation,)
(we lashed out
and hurt each other again.)
(But that wasn't what we intended.)
(We both longed to help each other,)
(but hated how powerless we were.)
(I've been thinking.)
(Everyone's most comfortable level of intimacy)
(is probably different.)
♪If the sky♪
♪And the sea♪
♪Turned upside down♪
♪If a swimming fish♪
♪Fell in love with a flying bird♪
♪If back then♪
♪We had never let go♪
♪We wouldn't be lost in the crowd♪
♪We met in a thirteenth month♪
♪Held each other in a fifth season♪
♪And found our way back whole♪
♪So let this surging love♪
♪Rise like tides that never fall♪
♪If we're caught in a pouring rain♪
♪That's alright♪
♪If we're buried♪
♪By passing years all the better♪
♪At least we still can keep♪
♪This one eternal photograph♪
♪We're on misaligned tracks♪
♪Running in opposite ways♪
♪Searching all along the way♪
♪For the fire of our younger hearts♪
♪And the beauty lost in time♪
♪This time don't lose each other again♪
♪Only after loss♪
♪Do we learn what truly matters most♪
♪In another time and space♪
♪We'll stay and walk together♪
♪Till we grow old♪
♪But still the sky will never♪
♪Turn with the sea♪
♪But still a swimming fish won't♪
♪Fall in love with a flying bird♪